Already after a couple of weeks, small green balls appeared -
where the rhubarb leaves stretched after the sun
Then came the drought.
The muddy soil that I touched around solidified to a hard crust
And burst into a grid pattern so my rhubarb jam looked like the pictures from a drying disaster in Africa.
null
The rhubarb cannot be able to get through.
But it made the weeds.
Admittedly, the quick root had to make an effort, but thistles and the horse hood seemed to be happy.
The plan was excellent.
I had spent a lot of time pondering how I want a sensible hen house that would work just as well
For me as for the chickens.
It was the reality that was the problem.
I want dense walls in the hen house because pulls are worse than cold for chickens
But when I started to put up slices on the walls, the screws did not attach.
The old wood was rotten.
And when I started changing the old board wall, the rules behind were also rotten.
The sill was the route.
So I had to make a decision for how carefully I would be with the renovation.
Chicken house renovation is starting to grow uncontrolled.
To nail over the rotten wood would do all renovation to wasted work that must
Made about the day the barn began to sack together.
So I changed the sill and I changed rules.
And the project I set aside for a week for just rolled on.
Every rotting plank I removed revealed more and more work.
Meanwhile, the weeds were flourished in my rhubarb cultivation.
The chickens were hatched and began to grow.
After a week, the chickens are no longer allowed because they dust.
It is a fact that perhaps only chicken owners know.
Chicken birds - however nice they are - have the ability to create a dust layer that settles
Everywhere in the room they live in.
The chicken move to the guest cottage was just a temporary solution.
So on the list of jobs that was in a hurry, I therefore had to add a new point: to create a temporary
Accommodation for the chickens.
The renovation of the chicken house was stopped and instead I started rebuilding the old pigsty
to temporary chicken accommodation.
Now I ignore the rotting planks but just slammed slices on the walls.
Put nets over the old rat holes, compost grates over all other openings and a plastic mat on the floor.
On with litter and then the chickens had to move in.
And the weeds grew.
It will never be as you imagined.
null